[
	{
		"question": "What treatments are available for kidney failure?",
		"options": [
			"Dialysis",
			"Kidney Transplant",
			"Both",
			"Neither"
		],
		"answer": 2
	},
	{
		"question": "Where is bile stored?",
		"options": [
			"Liver",
			"Stomach",
			"Gallbladder",
			"Appendix"
		],
		"answer": 2
	},
	{
		"question": "What is a collection of blood outside of blood vessels called?",
		"options": [
			"Hemorrhage",
			"Hematoma",
			"Dysthymia",
			"Cephalgia"
		],
		"answer": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "Which hormone results in feeling happy and thus also known as \"Happy Hormone\"?",
		"options": [
			"Dopamine",
			"epinephrine",
			"Luteinising",
			"Adrenocorticotrophic Hormone"
		],
		"answer": 0
	},
	{
		"question": "What does the medical term \"Myocardial Infarction\" refer to?",
		"options": [
			"Liver Failure",
			"Brain Tumor",
			"Collapsed Lung",
			"Heart Attack"
		],
		"answer": 3
	},
	{
		"question": "When should you start Chest Compressions?",
		"options": [
			"When the patient is not feeling well",
			"When the patient is feeling dizzy & nauseous",
			"When the patient has no pulse or breathing",
			"When the patient has lost a lot of blood"
		],
		"answer": 2
	},
	{
		"question": "Which of these is not a good bacteria?",
		"options": [
			"Lactobacillus",
			"Bifidobacteria",
			"Staphylococcus",
			"Saccharomyces boulardii"
		],
		"answer": 2
	},
	{
		"question": "Which part of the body never grows from birth to death?",
		"options": [
			"Cornea",
			"Intestines",
			"Appendix",
			"The Midbrain"
		],
		"answer": 0
	},
	{
		"question": "What are the neurons connected through?",
		"options": [
			"Axon",
			"Synapses",
			"Dendrites",
			"Albumin"
		],
		"answer": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "Which is the longest bone in the human body?",
		"options": [
			"Sternum",
			"Vertebrae",
			"Femur",
			"Stapes"
		],
		"answer": 2
	}
]